# Ivy Nah

Software Developer

An all-rounder with experience in team management, operations management as well as technical skills in electrical engineering and software development. Proficient in people skills, understanding client's requirements and operational needs.

Just completed a 6-month full-time certification course in Software Development Immersive, accredited by NTU in preparation for my career step as a Software Developer.

## **Programming Project Experience**

NTU (6 months full-time) - Projects done with a group of 4 other coursemates.

Project 1 - SG Gai Gai

Built a website using ReactJS to check local transport data using APIs from LTA.

Project 2, 3 and Capstone Project - HabitHobbit Mobile App

- Built a Habits Tracker API with PostgreSQL.
- Migrated habits tracker API to MongoDB and created an app to register a user, login and create habits using React Native.
- Expanded the features of HabitHobbit app to include a dashboard, profile page, activity feed, and the ability to edit the profile and habits.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Certis Cisco** — Auxiliary Police Officer (Enforcement)

Sept 2020 - Dec 2021

Deployed at Tuas Checkpoint to assist client in enforcement security operations.

- Led a team of 10–16 officers and ensured that daily operations are run smoothly.
- Liaised with clients to ensure successful implementations of special operations.
- Handled cases or disputes on ground as and when needed.
- In charge of daily and monthly deployment as an Operation Planner.

## **Esplanade** — Technical Crew (Part-time)

July 2019 - Sept 2020

- Understand stage lighting requirements from both client and lighting designer.
- Setup/strike lighting rigs before and after shows working both independently and in teams.

## **Privé** — Service Supervisor

July 2016 - Nov 2018

- Managed daily cafe operations including supervision of around 10 ground staff, opening and closing, briefing staff on daily specials and ensuring all guests special requests are communicated.
- Unified daily sales using POS system.
- Managed payroll of part-time staff.

91196743 https://github.com/ivynah

### **Coding Skills**

HTML, CSS

Javascript

**Bootstrap** 

ReactIS

ReactNative

PostgreSQL

MongoDB

### **Education**

**Bachelor of Arts in Tourism and Events** Management, **Murdoch University** 

Sept 2014 - Oct 2016

**Diploma in Electrical Engineering with** Specialization in Audio-Visual Technology, Ngee Ann Polytechnic

April 2011 - May 2014